http://www.babynamescountry.com/privacy_policy.html

Privacy Policy
We understand your need to maintain your privacy when using the Internet for your communication, shopping, exploration, and play.That's why the BabyNamesCountry.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices only for this web site.
Links to partner and advertiser sites
The BabyNamesCountry.com contains links to advertiser and partner websites. Please be aware that BabyNamesCountry.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites and we do not control the practices of any of our advertisers or partners to whom we are linked. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website.
Advertisers
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Kids' Privacy
We're committed to protecting the safety and privacy of all our users, especially those who are under 13. To this end, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (16 C.F.R. Part 312). We do not collect or display the individually identifying information of users who are under the age of 13.
If you would like to learn more about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, please visit the Federal Trade Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/kidsprivacy.htm.
Notification of Changes
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the website. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. So please check back here regularly to get our latest privacy policy.
IP Address
An IP address is a unique number assigned to your computer when you are browsing the internet. Your IP address is used only in order to analyze traffic on our web site, to provide you with content relevant to your area and to manage our web site.
Tell a Friend
When you recommending our site to your friends, we ask for both your email address and your friend's. We not share this information with third parties and we do not collect or use e-mail addresses of the senders or the recipients for any purposes.
What are Cookies?
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide useful features for their users. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. For more information on cookies, please visit http://www.cookiecentral.com.
We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You are always free to instruct your web browser to decline our cookies if it has the capability to do so, but some parts of our Site (Favorite Names Section) may not work properly if you do.
Contact Us
If you have any questions and comments about this privacy statement, feel free to Contact Us.
Baby Names Country - Origins and Meanings of Names from all over the World!
Copyright © 2006 - 2012 BabyNamesCountry.com. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy | Terms of Service
